GANNAVARAPU SAI ADITYA

Machine Learning Fellow Fellowship.Al Bengaluru, India Phone: +91 - 7032523251

Website GitHub LinkedIn adityagannavarapu.67@gmail.com

PROJECTS

Drawing with Machines, implementing Sketch RNN (Website)

Implemented using p5.js and sketch_rnn.js of Magenta, an open source research project exploring the role of machine learning as a tool in the creative process. Sketch RNN is trained on Quick Draw! doodle dataset of Google. It is generative model for vector drawings. If you start a drawing, it will finish it for you.

Gesture Pong, Gesture Controlled Pong game using Tensorflow.js and Object Detection API (Website)

Using TensorFlow Object detection API, created a game which can be controlled using the gestures of your hand from video in front of webcam. Wave your hand in front of webcam to control the paddle. Inspired from the implementation of Victor Dibia.

3D visualization of Furniture using three.js, deployed to Heroku (Website)

This is an e-commerce store which can help the user to visualize furniture in 3D using three.js. 3D models were made Blender and consumed them into the application using three.js to visualize in different ways and add different fabrics to the existing model.

Car Drive - 3D, a simple game developed in the style of GTA 1(Website)

Using three.js, CSS3DRenderer built a simple top view car drive game similar to GTA 1.

Speech Recognition (Wake-word Detection with a chime) (Video Demo)

This is a demo that I've developed to recognize audio commands and trained a model on a wake word to start taking audio input and converting it into text to derive intents using NLP.

Image Style Transfer using TensorFlow.js (Website)

This is an implementation of Neural Artistic Style Transfer running in browser using Tensorflow.js. This was inspired by the research paper <u>A Neural Algorithm of Artistic Style</u>. Converted the trained model to javascript using tensorflow.js and used it for running in a browser.

Aranii Sansthan, NGO focusing on young children (Website)

Designed and developed a fully functional website for Aranii Sansthan, NGO under the guidance of Dr. Ashu Bhardwaj, Humanities Professor at MNIT, Jaipur.

For more projects, please visit my personal website or Codepen profile.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE		
Sep, 2019 – Dec, 2019	ML Fellow, Fellowship.AI As a Machine Learning Fellow, I'm working on developing a solution for fire hazard problem, which classifies scenes from a given video/image input into classes of hazard or non-hazard.	
July, 2018 – August,2019	Specialist Programmer, Infosys I was a full-stack developer working on React, Angular and .NET. I was the front-end lead for a team of three working on developing enterprise web applications in React.	
2016 - 2017 2015 - 2016	Technical Secretary, MNIT SPORTS FESTIVAL, Annual Sports Fest. Consecutively held this position for two years. Designed and Developed the website of MST, a responsive, mobile-friendly and dynamic website.	
Aug - Nov,2016	Full-Stack Developer Intern, Third Dimension. Worked as a Full-Stack Developer in developing an e-commerce furniture website which uses Laravel, a PHP framework and POSTGRESQL in the back-end.	

EDUCATION			
2014-18	Graduation, Electrical Engineering Malaviya National Institute of Technology, Jaipur	(On a scale of 10) 5.27	
2012-14	Intermediate/+2 (Senior Secondary Education) Board of Intermediate Education Andhra Pradesh	95.4%	
2011-12	Matriculation (Central Board of Secondary Education)	(On a scale of 10) 9.8	

SKILL SET AND INTERESTS

- Programming Languages C, C++, Python, JavaScript, PHP.
- Front-End Web Development involving Angular, React, HTML, CSS, jQuery, JS.
- Back-End Web Development involving .NET, PHP, MySQL, PHP Frameworks (LARAVEL),
- Machine Learning Regression, One-Shot Learning, Deep Learning, K-NN, SVM, Cluster Analysis, NLP, LSTM, GRU RNN, CNN
- Interests in Computer Vision, Reinforcement Learning, Genomics, GAN (General Adversarial Networks)

RELEVANT INFORMATION			
Courses	Completed Andrew NG's Machine Learning Course(Coursera) and Deep Learning Course (deeplearning.ai).		
Languages	English (working proficiency), Hindi (working proficiency), Telugu (Native).		

EXTRACURRICULLARS

- Technical Secretary, Electrical Engineering Society(EES), Student Body of Electrical Engineering Department, MNIT Jaipur.
- Web Head, MNIT SPORTS TOURNAMENT-2015, Annual Sports Fest.

PASTIME

- Playing Football
- Digital Art